vendini.com 2019-07-03

# Privacy -

Vendini, Inc. (“Vendini”) provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from users of our ticketing, patron management, marketing and fund raising services (each a “Vendini Service”), our website located at www.vendini.com and its subdomains (“Site”) and any other services offered by Vendini in connection with a Vendini Service or the Site (any and all of the foregoing the “Services”). This Privacy Policy applies only to information that you provide to us through the Services.

## Information Collection: Personally Identifiable Information

  * In the course of using the Services, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you and administer your use and enjoyment of the Services (“Personal Information”). Personal Information may include, but is not limited to, your name and email address. We use your Personal Information primarily to provide the Services and administer your inquiries.
  * We may also collect the other information that you provide as part of registration and the administration and personalization of your user experience (such as zip code or location and individual preferences) (“Non-Identifying Information”).
  * We use your Personal Information (in some cases, in conjunction with your Non-Identifying Information) primarily to provide the Services and administer your inquiries. Certain Non-Identifying Information would be considered a part of your Personal Information if it were combined with other identifiers (such as combining your zip code with your street address) in a way that enables you to be identified. But the same pieces of information are considered Non-Identifying Information when they are taken alone or combined only with other non- identifying information (such as your viewing preferences). We may combine your Personal Information with Non-Identifying Information and aggregate it with information collected from other Vendini users to attempt to provide you with a better experience, to improve the Services and to analyze and understand how the Services are used. We may also use the combined information without aggregating it to serve you specifically, for instance, to deliver a product to you according to your preferences or restrictions.
  * We also use your Personal Information to contact you with Vendini newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications.

### Surveys and Promotions

From time to time, we may provide you the opportunity to participate in surveys, contests or offers (any of these a “Promotion”) via our Site or Services. If you participate in a Promotion we will request certain Personal Information from you. We use the Personal Information you provide to us in these instances to administer your participation in the Promotion. Participation in a Promotion is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information.

### Log Data

When you use our Services (such as when you visit our Site or interact with a Vendini Service), our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website or service connected to the Internet (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s, or other mobile device’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, the webpage you were visiting before you came to our Site, pages of our Site that you visit, the time spent on those pages, sections of our applications that you access, information you search for on our Site, access times and dates, and other statistics. We use this information to monitor and analyze use of the Site and Services for technical administration and tailoring our Services to our users’ needs.

## Our Policy Toward Children

IF YOU ARE UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE, THEN PLEASE DO NOT USE OR ACCESS THE SERVICES AT ANY TIME OR IN ANY MANNER.

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, Vendini does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information from persons under 13 years-of-age. If Vendini learns that personally-identifiable information of persons less than 13-years-of-age has been collected on or through the Services, then Vendini will take the appropriate steps to delete this information.

If you are the parent or legal guardian of a child under 13 who uses the Services, then please contact Vendini at [support@vendini.com](mailto:support@vendini.com) to have that child’s information deleted.

## Cookies and Other Technologies

Like many websites, we use “cookies” to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes. We may use “persistent cookies” to save a username and login password for future logins to the Site and differentiate you from another patron. We also may use “session ID cookies” to enable certain features of the Site or Services, to better understand how you interact with the Site and to monitor web traffic routing on the Site and aggregate usage of the Site and Services. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Site or all functionality of the Services.

We may also use “pixel tags,” “web beacons,” “clear GIFs” or similar means (individually or collectively “Pixel Tags”) in connection with our Services to collect usage, demographic and geographical location data. A Pixel Tag is an electronic image, often a single pixel, that is ordinarily not visible to users and may be associated with cookies on a user’s hard drive. Pixel Tags allow us to count users who have visited certain pages of the Site, to deliver branded services and to help determine the effectiveness of promotional or advertising campaigns.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

WE WILL NOT SHARE, SELL, RENT, OR TRADE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION WITH OTHER PARTIES EXCEPT AS PROVIDED BELOW:

Aggregate Information and Non-Identifying Information. We may share aggregated information that includes non-identifying information and Log Data with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling, and to deliver targeted advertising about other products and services. Any aggregated information shared in these contexts will not contain your Personal Information.

### Services Providers

We employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Services (such as credit card processing services, maintenance services, database management, web analytics and improvement of our Services’ features), to provide the Services on our behalf, or to assist us in analyzing how Services are used. These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

### Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement

We may disclose any information about you if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws (such as U.S. Copyright law) or respond to a court order, judicial or other government subpoena, or warrant in the manner required by the requesting entity.

### Information For Which You Have Provided Consent

We will share Personal Information with certain third parties provided that you have consented to such sharing pursuant to a separate agreement between you and us (such as in any license agreements which you have accepted for our mobile applications, including Walletini).

### Companies Using Our Services

We may share your email address with the company or organization for whose event you are purchasing a ticketing using our Services. In such case, you will be subject to that company’s or organization’s privacy policy with respect to their use of this information.

Vendini also reserves the right to disclose information that we believe, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to take precautions against liability; protect Vendini from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful uses; to investigate and defend ourselves against third-party claims or allegations; to assist government enforcement agencies; to protect the security or integrity of the Services; enforce our Terms of Use; or to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Vendini, our users, or others.

## Business Transfers

Vendini may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your Personal Information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy.

## Security

We are concerned with the security of your Personal Information and are committed to taking reasonable steps to protect it from unauthorized access and use. To that end, we put in place the appropriate physical, electronic and managerial policies and procedures designed to secure Personal Information, including Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software to secure commerce transaction. We also continue to implement procedures to maintain accurate, complete and current Personal Information. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is one hundred percent secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

We will make any legally required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored “personal data” (as defined in applicable state statutes on security breach notification) to you via email or conspicuous posting on the Site in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, insofar as consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system.

## Phishing

Identity theft and the practice currently known as “phishing” are of great concern to Vendini. Safeguarding information to help protect you from identity theft is a top priority. We do not and will not, at any time, request your credit card information, your account ID, login password, or national identification numbers in a non-secure or unsolicited e-mail or telephone communication. For more information about phishing, visit the Federal Trade Commission’s website.

## International Transfer

Your information may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, Vendini transfers Personal Information to the United States and processes it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

## Links to Other Sites

Our Services my contain links to other websites and online services. The fact that we link to a website, content or present a banner ad or other type of advertisement is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices. We do not exercise control over third party websites or services. These other websites or services may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. Other websites and services follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites and services you use.

## Changes and Updates to this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy may be revised periodically, and this will be reflected by a “last modified” date below. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. When we modify this Privacy Policy, we will make reasonable efforts to notify you (e.g. by email or by means of a notice on our homepage). Our amended Privacy Policy will automatically take effect 30 days after we provide notice of the change, except that (i) we will not, without your consent, use your previously collected personally identifiable information in a manner inconsistent Privacy Policy in effect when we received that information, and (ii) if you do not agree with any changes to the Privacy Policy, you may terminate your account ceasing use of the Services.

## Changes and Updates to this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy was last modified on March 19, 2013

## Vendini Contact Information

Please contact Vendini with any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, your personal information, and our third-party disclosure practices at: Vendini, Inc., 55 Francisco St. Suite 350, San Francisco, California 94133, USA or by email at [support@vendini.com](mailto:support@vendini.com). We will make every effort to respond to your inquiry within 30 days of its receipt.
